{
    "subject": "resource/Constant_Huysmans",
    "predicate": "ontology/birthPlace",
    "object": "resource/Antwerp",
    "human_readable": "Constant Huysmans was born in Antwerp.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8294561505317688,
            "question": "Where was Constant Huysmans born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8085545301437378,
            "question": "Name the city where Constant Huysmans was born."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5237261056900024,
            "question": "What is Constant Huysmans known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3986192047595978,
            "question": "What era was Constant Huysmans a prominent figure in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.38028189539909363,
            "question": "In what country was Antwerp located?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3621159493923187,
            "question": "Was Constant Huysmans a famous writer?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3609280288219452,
            "question": "Is there any information about Constant Huysmans' early life?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3401690423488617,
            "question": "Did Constant Huysmans have any notable influences?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.30234387516975403,
            "question": "What were some of Constant Huysmans' most famous works?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.23154298961162567,
            "question": "Can you tell me about Constant Huysmans' writing style?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Constant Huysmans was born in Antwerp.",
            "html": "dbpedia_8228_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What were some of Constant Huysmans' most famous works?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8228_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Did Constant Huysmans have any notable influences?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8228_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is there any information about Constant Huysmans' early life?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8228_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8228_16.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8228_18.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8228_21.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8228_22.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8228_25.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8228_46.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8228_50.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8228_51.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8228_58.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8228_62.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'} \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the evaluation of the triple:\n\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n\nThe documents indicate that Constant Huysmans was indeed born in Antwerp, according to the information in file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_8228/re-ranker-msmarco/19.txt."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents state that \"Place of Birth\" for Constant Huysmans is listed as Antwerp, which directly supports the statement that Constant Huysmans was born in Antwerp."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"no\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Extremely Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "mistral": {
            "reason": "Huysmans was born in Paris, not Antwerp.",
            "category": 2
        }
    }
}